http://www.jfahern.com/legal

Skip to main content
You are hereHomeLegal
Legal
Terms of Use
Welcome to the J. F. Ahern Co. web sites, which include but are not limited to www.jfahern.com (the "Sites"). The Sites are provided as a service to our customers. Please review the following terms and conditions of use, which govern your use of the Sites (the "Agreement").
Your use of the Sites constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Agreement. We reserve the right to update or modify this Agreement at any time without prior notice. For this reason, we encourage you to review the Agreement whenever you use any of the Sites. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Sites.
Right to Change Sites
We reserve the right, at any time in our sole discretion, to: modify, suspend or discontinue the Sites or any service, content, feature or product offered through the Sites, with or without notice; charge fees in connection with the use of the Sites; modify and/or waive any fees charged in connection with the Sites; and/or offer opportunities to some or all users of the Sites. You agree that we shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Site, or any service, content, feature or product offered through the Sites.
SiteContents
Unless otherwise noted, the Sites, and all materials on the Sites, including text, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips and other materials, and the copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property in such materials (collectively, the "Contents"), are owned, controlled or licensed by J. F. Ahern Co. and other trademarks appearing on the Sites are the trademarks of J. F. Ahern Co. and/or its subsidiaries.
The Sites and the Contents are intended solely for commercial, non-personal use. You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Sites for your personal business use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded Content is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or exploit in any way any of the Contents or the Sites.
User Comments, Feedback, and Other Submissions
J. F. Ahern Co. is pleased to hear from users and welcomes your comments regarding our products and services. J. F. Ahern Co.'s company policy does not allow us to accept or to consider creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials other than those we have specifically requested. We hope that you will understand that the intent of this policy is to avoid the possibility of future misunderstandings when projects developed by J. F. Ahern Co.'s employees and agents might seem to be similar to creative works submitted by users. Accordingly, while we value your feedback, we must ask that you do not send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials for our business. If, at our request, you send certain specific submissions (for example contest entries) or without out a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, "Comments"), you agree that J. F. Ahern Co. may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate, and otherwise use in any medium any Comments that you forward to J. F. Ahern Co.. J. F. Ahern Co. is and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any Comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any Comments; or (3) to respond to any Comments. J. F. Ahern Co. has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any Comments.
You agree that your Comments will not violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your Comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of the Sites. You may not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself, or otherwise mislead J. F. Ahern Co. or third parties as to the origin of any Comments. You are solely responsible for any Comments you make and their accuracy. J. F. Ahern Co. takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any Comments posted by your or any third party.
Personal Information Submitted Through the Sites
Your submission of personal information through the Sites is governed by our privacy policy, which can be reached by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" link located in the footer section of the Sites (the "Privacy Policy"). This Agreement incorporates by reference the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy.
Errors, Inaccuracies, and Omissions
Occasionally there may be information on our Sites that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, promotions, offers, and availability. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information or cancel orders if any information on the Sites is inaccurate at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order).
Termination
These terms are effective unless and until terminated by either you or J. F. Ahern Co. You may terminate this Agreement at any time. J. F. Ahern Co. also may terminate this Agreement at any time without notice, and accordingly may deny you access to the Sites, if in our sole judgment you fail to comply with any term or provision of the Agreement. The obligations and liabilities of the parties incurred prior to the termination date shall survive the termination of this Agreement for all purposes.
State Business and Professional Licenses
Click here to view our state business and professional licenses.
J. F. AHERN CO.
Corporate Headquarters
© 2020 J. F. Ahern Co. All rights reserved.
855 Morris Street
Fond du Lac, WI 54935
800.532.4376
Contact
Click Here for Payment
Alarm Monitor Login
Privacy
Legal
Search
Main menuMulti-Trade Services BackMulti-Trade Services By Location BackAppletonChicagoDavenportDes MoinesEau ClaireFond du LacMilwaukeeHolmenMadisonMarinetteOmahaPeoriaSt. LouisTwin CitiesPipe Fabrication BackPipe Fabrication ShopPlumbing BackPlumbing Fabrication ShopPreventive Maintenance BackFire Preventive MaintenanceHVAC Preventive MaintenancePlumbing Preventive MaintenanceHVAC BackSheet Metal Fabrication ShopBuilding ControlsBuilding Commissioning ServicesBuilding Energy SolutionsMulti-Trade Modular PrefabricationIndustrial Services BackIndustrial Services Fabrication ShopPreconstruction ServicesFire Protection & Life Safety BackFire Protection Fabrication ShopFire Alarm & ControlFire SprinklerFire Suppression BackCarbon DioxideInert GasFoam Fire SuppressionWet ChemicalDry ChemicalClean AgentWatermist Fire SuppressionFire EquipmentSafetyIndustries BackAgricultureAlternative/Biofuel FacilitiesAssisted Living/Nursing HomesBiotechnologyBreweries/DistilleriesChemical/Industrial PlantsCold StorageCorrectional FacilitiesData CentersEducational FacilitiesEntertainment FacilitiesFood/BeverageGovernmentHealthcareHigh-Rise/Multi HousingLaboratories/PharmaceuticalLodgingManufacturingMining OperationsMuseumsOffices/Commercial BuildingsPipelinePower GenerationPublishing/PrintingPulp & PaperRefineriesReligious FacilitiesResidentialRestaurantsRetailTransportationWarehousing/DistributionWater/WastewaterProjectsAbout Us BackCore IdeologyAwardsHistorySocial ResponsibilityBlogUtility Menu800.532.4376After Hours EmergencyContact Us BackAppleton, WisconsinChicago, IllinoisDavenport, IowaDes Moines, IowaEau Claire, WisconsinFond du Lac, WisconsinHolmen, WisconsinMadison, WisconsinMarinette, WisconsinMilwaukee, WisconsinOmaha, NebraskaPeoria, IllinoisSt. Louis, MissouriTwin Cities, MinnesotaNews
